Like và share page htttp://www.fb.com/AegisubVietNam/ để ủng hộ chúng tôi phát triển hơn nữa
Lately I've been thinking about what I can do
I've been stressing to fall back in love with you
I'm so sorry that I couldn't follow through
But I can't go on this way.
I've got to stop it babe
You've been wonderful in all that you can be
But it hurts when you say that you understand me
So believe me.
I, I am sorry, I,
I am sorry, I, I
I wanted you to be there when I fall
I wanted you to see me through it all
I wanted you to be the one I loved
I wanted you
I wanted you to hold me in my sleep
I wanted you to show me what I need
I wanted you to know just how down deep
I wanted you
I've been pushing hard to open up the door
Trying to take us back to where we were before
But I'm done.
I just can't do this anymore
Cuz we can't be mended, so let's stop pretending now
We've been walking around in circles for some time
And I think we should head for the finish line
So believe me.
I, I am sorry, I,
I am sorry, I
I wanted you to be there when I fall
I wanted you to see me through it all
I wanted you to be the one I loved
I wanted you
I wanted you to hold me in my sleep
I wanted you to show me what I need
I wanted you to know just how down deep
I wanted you
I, I.. I'm so sorry baby
But I, I.. I gotta pack up and leave
But I, I'll always remember how we came close
..to being how I wanted to be
I wanted you baby
I wanted you
I wanted you to be there when I fall
I wanted you to see me through it all
I wanted you to be the one I loved
I wanted you
I wanted you to hold me in my sleep
I wanted you to show me what I need
I wanted you to know just how down deep
I wanted you
I wanted you...BABY...
I wanted you...
I wanted you, I wanted you...