Caûm giaùc gì theá naøy?
What is this I'm feeling
Em chaúng theå giaûi thích noåi
I just can't explain
Khi coù anh keà beân
When you're near
Em chaúng gioáng luùc thöôøng nöõa
I'm just not the same
Em ñang coá che giaáu
I'm trying to hide it
Coá khoâng cho anh bieát
Try not to show it
Thaät ñieân roà
It's crazy
Sao laïi theá nhæ
How could it be
Em ñaõ phaûi loøng anh roài
I've fallen for you
Cuoái cuøng, con tim em ñaõ môû loøng
Finally, my heart gave in
Vaø em chìm ñaém trong tình yeâu
And I'm fallen in love
Cuoái cuøng em cuõng hieåu caûm giaùc aáy
I finally know how it feels
Khi anh noùi " chaøo em"
When you said hello
Em nhìn vaøo ñoâi maét anh
I looked in your eyes
Chôït, em thaáy thoaûi maùi trong loøng
Suddenly, I felt good inside
Vaäy laø ñieàu aáy ñaõ xaûy ra thaät roài
Is this really happening
Hay em chæ ñang mô?
Or am I just dreaming
Em ñoaùn, ñoù laø söï thaät
I guess, it's true
Em chaúng theå tin ñöôïc
I can't believe
Em ñaõ phaûi loøng anh roài
I've fallen for you
Cuoái cuøng, con tim em ñaõ môû loøng
Finally, my heart gave in
Vaø em chìm ñaêm trong tình yeâu
And I'm fallen in love
Cuoái cuøng em cuõng hieåu caûm giaùc aáy
I finally know how it feels
Thì ra ñaây laø tinh yeâu
So this is love
Duø em ôû nôi ñaâu
Doesn't matter where I am
Nhöõng nghó suy veà anh vaãn hieän höõu trong taâm trí em
Thoughts of you still linger in my mind
Khoâng caàn bieát laø maáy giôø nöõa
No matter what time of day
Em ñaõ thaät söï, thaät söï
I've really, really
Phaûi loøng anh roài
Fallen for you
Em ñaõ phaûi loøng anh roài
I've fallen for you
Cuoái cuøng, con tim em ñaõ môû loøng
Finally, my heart gave in
Vaø em chìm ñaêm trong tình yeâu
And I'm fallen in love
Cuoái cuøng em cuõng hieåu caûm giaùc aáy
I finally know how it feels
Em ñaõ phaûi loøng anh
I've fallen for you
Cuoái cuøng, con tim em ñaõ môû loøng
Finally, my heart gave in
Vaø em chìm ñaêm trong tình yeâu
And I'm fallen in love
Cuoái cuøng em cuõng hieåu caûm giaùc aáy
I finally know how it feels
Thì ra ñaây laø tình yeâu...
So this is love