You're so hypnotizing
Could you be the devil, could you be an angel
Your touch magnetizing
Feels like going floating, leave my body glowing
They say be afraid
You're not like the others, futuristic lovers
Different DNA, they don't understand
You're from a another world
A different dimension
You open my eyes
And im ready to go, lead me into the light
Kiss me, kiss, kiss, kiss me
Infect me with your love, and fill me with your poison
Take me, take, take, take me
Wanna be your victim, ready for abduction
Boy, you're an alien, your touch so far away
It's supernatural, extraterrestrial
You're so super sonic
Wanna feel your powers, stumb me with your lasers
Your kiss is cosmic, every move is magic
You're from a another world
A different dimension
You open my eyes
And im ready to go, lead me into the light
Kiss me, kiss, kiss, kiss me
Infect me with your love, and fill me with your poison
Take me, take, take, take me
Wanna be your victim, ready for abduction
Boy, you're an alien, your touch so far away
It's supernatural, extraterrestrial
There is this transcendental, on another level
Boy, you're my lucky star
I wanna walk on your wave length
And be there when you vibrate
For you i risk it all
All
Kiss me, kiss, kiss, kiss me
Infect me with your love, and fill me with your poison
Take me, take, take, take me
Wanna be your victim, ready for abduction
Boy, you're an alien, your touch so far away
It's supernatural, extraterrestrial
Extraterrestrial
Boy, you're an alien, your touch so far away
It's supernatural, extraterrestrial