When I said go I never meant away
khi em baûo anh ñi em khoâng bao giôø coù nghó gi xa xoâi
You ought to know the freaky games we play
anh neân hieåu chuùng ta ñang chôi 1 troø chôi thaät kyø laï
could you forgive and learn how to forget
anh coù theå tha thöù vaø ñöøng ñeå buïng khoâng?
hear me as I'm calling out your name
laéng nghe khi em goïi teân anh
Firefly come back to me
ñom ñoùm ôi haõy quay veà beân em
make the night as bright as day
khieán maø ñeâm raïng ngôøi nhö buoåi sôùm
I'll be looking out for you
em seõ maõi ñôïi chôø anh
tell me that your lonely too
haõy noùi em nghe raèng anh cuõng ñang coâ ñôn
firefly come lead me on
ñom ñoùm ôi haõy ñeán laøm em vöõng tin
follow you into the sun
em seõ theo anh höôùng tôùi anh raïng ñoâng
that's the way it ought to be
ñoù laø con ñöôøng em vaãn mong chôø
firefly come back to me
ñom ñoùm ôi haõy veà beân em
You and me
anh vaø em
we shared a mystery
cuøng chia seõ nhöõng bí maät
we were so close
vaø gaén boù vôùi nhau
like honey to the bee
nhö maät ngoït chaúng khi naøo rôøi xa
And if you tell me how to make you understand
vaø neáu anh hoûi em laøm sao ñeå anh hieåu ñöôïc
I'm minor in a major kinda way
em bieát noùi sao khi mình beù nhoû treân con ñöôøng roäng lôùn
Firefly come back to me
ñom ñoùm ôi veà laïi beân em
make the night as bright as day
toûa aùnh saùng xua ñi maøn ñeâm taêm toái
I'll be looking out for you
em seõ maõi ñôïi chôø anh
tell me that your lonely too
haõy noùi em nghe anh cuõng ñang coâ ñôn
firefly come lead me on
ñom ñoùm ôi daãn loái cho em nheù
follow you into the sun
em seõ theo anh höôùng tôùi anh raïng ñoâng
that's the way it ought to be
ñoù laø con ñöông em vaãn haèng mong
firefly come back to me
ñom ñom ôi haõy trôû veà beân em
Fly firefly through the sky
bay xuyeân qua baàu trôøi
come and play with my desire
ñeán ñeán beân embeen con tim ñam meâ
don't be long don't ask why
ñöøng chaäm vaø ñöøng hoûi taïi sao
I can't wait another nighttttttt
em khoâng theå chôøi laâu hôn ñöôïc nöõa
wait another night
Firefly come back to me
make the night as bright as day
I'll be looking out for you
tell me that your lonely too
firefly come lead me on
follow you into the sun
that's the way it ought to be
Firefly come back
Firefly come back to me
make the night as bright as day
I'll be looking out for you
tell me that your lonely too
firefly come lead me on
follow you into the sun
that's the way it ought to be
Firefly come back to me